MoMA PS1 Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series I: Curatorial and Exhibition Records, (19682009)
  - Subseries I.A: General Files, (19702009)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Monica Bonvicini, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2583)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: BroFriedrich, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2584)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: BroFriedrich, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2585)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: De:Bug, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2586)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: De:Bug, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2587)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Thomas Demand, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 166, Folder I.A.2588)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Rineke Dijkstra, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 166, Folder I.A.2589)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Olafur Eliasson, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 166, Folder I.A.2590)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Olafur Eliasson, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Art and Event Photographs (Box 166, Folder I.A.2591)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Jurgen Frisch, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2592)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Peter Friedl, 1998-1999; Of the slides present, nearly all are marked "Berlin Biennial" 1998. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2593)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Peter Friedl, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 166, Folder I.A.2594)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: "Russell H. and Tara in Berlin", 1999; Correspondence. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2595)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Natascha Haghighian, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2596)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Christine Hill, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2597)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Carsten Hller, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 166, Folder I.A.2598)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Honey-Suckle Company, 1998-1999; 1 VHS tape in hand-decorated case only. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2599)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Honey-Suckle Company, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2600)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Johannes Kahrs, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2601)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Johannes Kahrs, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2602)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Christoph Keller, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2603)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Christoph Keller, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2604)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: David Lamelas, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms and shipping documents. (Box 167, Folder I.A.2605)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Xavier Le Roy, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2606)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: John de Maya, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2607)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Yana Milev, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2608)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Minimal Club B_Books, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2609)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Bert Neumann, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2610)
    - Children of Berlin Artist File: Bert Neumann, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2611)
    - Children of Berlin Artists File: Manfred Pernice, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 167, Folder I.A.2612)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Daniel Pflumm, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 167, Folder I.A.2613)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Daniel Pflumm, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Loan forms. (Box 167, Folder I.A.2614)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Neo Rauch, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2615)
    - Children of Berlin Artists File: Stefan Rethfeld, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2616)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Christoph Schlingensief, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2617)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Nick Schweiger/3 de Luxe, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2618)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Anatolij Shuravlev, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2619)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Anatolij Shuravlev, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2620)
    - Children of Berlin Artist Files: Starship, 1998-1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2621)
    - Children of Berlin: Cookie's Bar, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2622)
    - Children of Berlin Damage Documents, 1999; Small amount of documents and correspondence regarding artwork damage. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 168, Folder I.A.2623)
    - 2000 and 2001 Curatorial Material, 2000-2001; Brochures and magazines from Children of Berlin, materials on artists for Some New Minds,a CD CV for Ricardo Ribenboim, and other stray documents and correspondence. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Printed Ephemera Special Projects (Spring 2000) (April 30, 2000-[unknown closing date]): General Exhibition Documentation Some New Minds(December 17, 2000-February 28, 2001): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2624)
    - Children of Berlin: Contact Lists and Correspondence, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2625)
    - Children of Berlin: "Shipping Inquiries", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 168, Folder I.A.2626)
    - Children of Berlin: "Berlin Senate", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2627)
    - Children of Berlin: "Flights", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2628)
    - Children of Berlin: "To Do", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2629)
    - Children of Berlin: Duggal, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2630)
    - Children of Berlin: Correspondence and Bibliography, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2631)
    - Children of Berlin: Frisch, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 168, Folder I.A.2632)
    - Children of Berlin: Nik Schweiger, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2633)
    - Children of Berlin: Loan Forms, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; Entire folder restricted. (Box 169, Folder I.A.2634)
    - Children of Berlin: Stylegames.com, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2635)
    - Children of Berlin: "Store@3 De Luxe", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2636)
    - Children of Berlin: "Lightbox Project", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2637)
    - Children of Berlin: "Contact Numbers", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2638)
    - Children of Berlin: "Sand in the Lobby Project", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2639)
    - Children of Berlin: "Budget", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2640)
    - Children of Berlin: "Yurt Information", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2641)
    - Children of Berlin: "Ellen", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2642)
    - Children of Berlin: "Larissa/General", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2643)
    - Children of Berlin: Sauerbruch and Hutton Architects, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2644)
    - Children of Berlin: "Latest", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2645)
    - Children of Berlin: Mikro, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2646)
    - Children of Berlin: "Video Services Information", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2647)
    - Children of Berlin: "C.B. Information", 1999; Correspondence, primarily concerning works by Olafur Eliasson. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2648)
    - Children of Berlin: Shipping Documents and Correspondence, 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 169, Folder I.A.2649)
    - Children of Berlin: "RWE, Culture Ink", 1999; Public relations materials. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2650)
    - Children of Berlin: "Iris Scheffler/Shipping", 1999; Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 169, Folder I.A.2651)
    - Children of Berlin Budget and German Project Descriptions, 1998-1999; Most of the documents in German. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 169, Folder I.A.2652)
    - Children of Berlin: "Jonathan Meese De-Install Return Shipment", 2000; Shipping and installation materials. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Restricted material removed: Shipping documents. (Box 169, Folder I.A.2653)
    - Children of Berlin: Konrad Fischer, 2000; Shipping and installation materials. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; Entire folder restricted. (Box 169, Folder I.A.2654)
    - Installation Files:Children of Berlin, 1999; Correspondence and installation notes and documents. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2655)
    - Children of Berlin Artists CVs, 1999; Numerous CVs and materials on participating artists. Children of Berlin: Cultural Developments 1989-1999(November 7, 1999-January 2, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2656)
    - Installation Files: Eric Boman, 1999; Two notes only. (Box 170, Folder I.A.2657)
    - Installation Files: Robert Brinker, 1999 (Box 170, Folder I.A.2658)
    - "Artists Lists", circa 1999; Miscellaneous correspondence and contact lists. (Box 170, Folder I.A.2659)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, 2000; Various staff memos and notes. (Box 170, Folder I.A.2660)
    - Press Packet Materials, circa 2000; Various program descriptions and news clippings. (Box 170, Folder I.A.2661)
    - Winter 1999/2000 Exhibition Binder, Includes exhibition texts, budgets, artists' CVs, research literature, catalogues, and correspondence. Special Projects (Winter 1999-2000) (December 1, 1999-February 27, 2000): Press Release; Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation Special Projects (Spring 2000) (April 30, 2000-[unknown closing date]): Art and Event Photographs; General Exhibition Documentation Rob Pruitt: "Evian Waterfall"(April 30-June 18, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation; General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2662)
    - Min Tanaka, 1999; Memos and correspondence. Min Tanaka: "Subject: Heuristic Ecdysis"(December 5-December 19, 1999): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2663)
    - Min Tanaka, 1999; Information on the artist, with some correspondence and other documents. Min Tanaka: "Subject: Heuristic Ecdysis"(December 5-December 19, 1999): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2664)
    - Min Tanaka, 2000; Small amount of correspondence and memos. Min Tanaka: "Subject: Heuristic Ecdysis"(December 5-December 19, 1999): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2665)
    - "Jeanne van Heeswijk Proposal", 1998-1999; Hotel New York(December 15, 1999-February 25, 2001): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2666)
    - Artist Files:Hotel New York, 1999-2001; Correspondence with diagram and inventory of the constructed hotel room. 1999: P.S.1 Studio Program Exhibition(February 7-April 3, 1999): General Exhibition Documentation Hotel New York(December 15, 1999-February 25, 2001): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 170, Folder I.A.2667)
    - Empty Museum Plans and Notes, circa 1999; Sketches, notes, and project description of the work Empty Museum by Ilya Kabakov and Emila (Box 170, Folder I.A.2668)
    - "Installation Shots Old", circa 1999; Unidentified snapshots of artworks and works on computer monitors; of unkown relation to any exhibition. (Box 171, Folder I.A.2669)
    - "Julie Becker Project", 1999; Materials on an apparently unrealized project. (Box 171, Folder I.A.2670)
    - Bathelemy Toguo, 1999; Two pieces of correspondence only. (Box 171, Folder I.A.2671)
    - "Artwork Release Forms 1/2000-Present", Release forms and other documents from early 2000. (Box 171, Folder I.A.2672)
    - "Past Programs: New York Show", 1999; Small amount of early documents on Greater New York. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2673)
    - "Past Programs:Greater New York InTech Lawsuit", 2000; Documents relating to a lawsuit brought by P.S. 1 in small claims court against the manufacturer of the Greater New York CD-ROM for reneging on their promise to cover the cost of publication; with copy of catalogue and CD-ROM. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2674)
    - Greater New York: Loan Forms, 2000; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): Loan Forms and Condition Reports; Entire folder restricted. (Box 171, Folder I.A.2675)
    - Greater New York: Checklist, 2000; Preliminary checklist of received works. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2676)
    - Greater New York: "Image Master List", 2000; Photocopies of artwork images. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2677)
    - Greater New York: "Press", 2000; Includes catalogue and postcards. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): Printed Ephemera; News Clippings (Box 171, Folder I.A.2678)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Carolyn Christov-Bakargiev", 1999; Includes schedule of studio visits. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2679)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Klaus Biesenbach", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2680)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Russell Haswell", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 171, Folder I.A.2681)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Laura Hoptman", 1999-2000; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2682)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Paolo Herkenhoff", 1999-2000; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2683)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Tom Finkelpearl", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2684)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Deborah Wye", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2685)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Feri Daftari", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2686)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Claudia Schmulke", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2687)
    - "Greater New York City-Wide Search: Assignments for Studio Visits from MoMA Submissions", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2688)
    - "Greater New York-Wide Search: New Slides List", 1999; Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2689)
    - Greater New York: "Process", 1999-2000; Spiral binder of notes. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2690)
    - Greater New York: "Selection Process", 1999-2000; Lists of artists, with some notes and correspondence. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2691)
    - Greater New York: "Selection Process", 1999-2000; Lists of artists, with some notes and correspondence. Greater New York(February 27-May 30, 2000): General Exhibition Documentation (Box 172, Folder I.A.2692)